---
http_interactions:
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://www.eventbrite.com/json/ticket?app_key=<EVENTBRITE_API_KEY>&user_key=<EVENTBRITE_USER_KEY>
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers: {}
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Server:
      - nginx
      Date:
      - Thu, 07 Aug 2014 15:09:18 GMT
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
      Connection:
      - keep-alive
      X-Xss-Protection:
      - 1; mode=block
      X-Content-Type-Options:
      - nosniff
      Expires:
      - Fri, 01 Jan 1990 00:00:00 GMT
      X-Service:
      - djc
      X-Ua-Compatible:
      - IE=edge
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Cache-Control:
      - no-cache, must-revalidate, no-cache="Set-Cookie", private
      P3p:
      - CP="NOI ADM DEV PSAi COM NAV OUR OTRo STP IND DEM"
      X-Frame-Options:
      - SAMEORIGIN
      Set-Cookie:
      - AN=; expires=Thu, 01-Jan-1970 00:00:00 GMT; Max-Age=0; Path=/
      - G=v%3D1%26i%3Dfa595a3a-5d2e-48a2-9d77-e05909cd9181%26a%3D4aa%26s%3DAPDvTK7TBDpxa27iSfZfGuf9MySl709qDw;
        Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:09:18 GMT; httponly; Path=/
      - SP=AGQgbbm5moE53YigAKtFPvhs-C1f3MVVnexVe5LE8kIYdYJREM-3NxNQ0eJ8sFwCUaUyaHjPZGAiDXflC3Sd_7uXE-xKRCdg9kX9mzKCJuXeupfipowJJMw0qH7XU_RQ1GTg3UUzxWrF1tZ4f4fEFTNEU_cFgdWvjp21PK5AmSzKLZW8Kv_1dzVTCbt7HJpCGwuOt2wNU1_syvqajKpBNPm3g_-xfS7LAWr79w9c7GdTVW_7BebxtOw;
        Domain=.eventbrite.com; httponly; Path=/
      - SS=AE3DLHSG0nwjhnv7zzWd-zEcbtp-SyH7Tg; Domain=.eventbrite.com; httponly; Path=/;
        secure
      - eblang=lo%3Den_US%26la%3Den-us; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015
        15:09:18 GMT; httponly; Path=/
      - mgref=typeins; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:09:18 GMT;
        httponly; Max-Age=31536000; Path=/
      - mgrefby=; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:09:18 GMT; httponly;
        Max-Age=31536000; Path=/
      Transfer-Enc<METRICS_API_USERNAME>ng:
      - chunked
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ! '{"error": {"error_type": "Request Error", "error_message": "Not a
        valid API command.  Please check the documentation."}}'
    http_version: 
  recorded_at: Thu, 07 Aug 2014 15:09:26 GMT
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://www.eventbrite.com/json/ticket_get?app_key=<EVENTBRITE_API_KEY>&user_key=<EVENTBRITE_USER_KEY>
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers: {}
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Server:
      - nginx
      Date:
      - Thu, 07 Aug 2014 15:10:08 GMT
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
      Connection:
      - keep-alive
      X-Xss-Protection:
      - 1; mode=block
      X-Content-Type-Options:
      - nosniff
      Expires:
      - Fri, 01 Jan 1990 00:00:00 GMT
      X-Service:
      - djc
      X-Ua-Compatible:
      - IE=edge
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Cache-Control:
      - no-cache, must-revalidate, no-cache="Set-Cookie", private
      P3p:
      - CP="NOI ADM DEV PSAi COM NAV OUR OTRo STP IND DEM"
      X-Frame-Options:
      - SAMEORIGIN
      Set-Cookie:
      - AN=; expires=Thu, 01-Jan-1970 00:00:00 GMT; Max-Age=0; Path=/
      - G=v%3D1%26i%3D551b461f-4e87-4da6-ac30-38fcb795b2ce%26a%3D4aa%26s%3DAPDvTK5dk_56ZBWz3vhY_Ac6MuWC30jsnQ;
        Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:10:08 GMT; httponly; Path=/
      - SP=AGQgbbkM212FehRwrsJunQUSuf3R8VEugW5aFR-sqrcMdumPE2qPoZH1ecGKHHX_2Fd1UXikJ3NQiv-Urh2YZTydDgP7Sthgu9Y1nKXAYgKjPHOb6IFCqoTh-BbtUizBNMFaLEBm-6KebDjmbzp6-7m57k1qB1wUMKD2jmoyRcG5qOTYox1RKcVNyI-dmL40X79XPO6KD9Ivr-_BU4CUWA28KdAJ-oVEgzgpfmx9vziHPWm5D5Kl_50;
        Domain=.eventbrite.com; httponly; Path=/
      - SS=AE3DLHTMRVtZSFMjsYway3M3Vi1rkjXP4Q; Domain=.eventbrite.com; httponly; Path=/;
        secure
      - eblang=lo%3Den_US%26la%3Den-us; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015
        15:10:08 GMT; httponly; Path=/
      - mgref=typeins; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:10:08 GMT;
        httponly; Max-Age=31536000; Path=/
      - mgrefby=; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:10:08 GMT; httponly;
        Max-Age=31536000; Path=/
      Transfer-Enc<METRICS_API_USERNAME>ng:
      - chunked
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ! '{"error": {"error_type": "Request Error", "error_message": "Not a
        valid API command.  Please check the documentation."}}'
    http_version: 
  recorded_at: Thu, 07 Aug 2014 15:10:16 GMT
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://www.eventbrite.com/json/event_get?app_key=<EVENTBRITE_API_KEY>&user_key=<EVENTBRITE_USER_KEY>
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers: {}
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Server:
      - nginx
      Date:
      - Thu, 07 Aug 2014 15:16:50 GMT
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
      Connection:
      - keep-alive
      X-Xss-Protection:
      - 1; mode=block
      X-Content-Type-Options:
      - nosniff
      Expires:
      - Fri, 01 Jan 1990 00:00:00 GMT
      X-Service:
      - djc
      X-Ua-Compatible:
      - IE=edge
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Cache-Control:
      - no-cache, must-revalidate, no-cache="Set-Cookie", private
      P3p:
      - CP="NOI ADM DEV PSAi COM NAV OUR OTRo STP IND DEM"
      X-Frame-Options:
      - SAMEORIGIN
      Set-Cookie:
      - AN=; expires=Thu, 01-Jan-1970 00:00:00 GMT; Max-Age=0; Path=/
      - G=v%3D1%26i%3D1dd67969-074e-4026-8903-2272ac613600%26a%3D4aa%26s%3DAPDvTK7sCcTTwIaWMCxSrAYyyWMtipaBtg;
        Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:16:50 GMT; httponly; Path=/
      - SP=AGQgbbnwAS8RA9UvFMIXMWYRKYG5ua6a8JG8Ur88utPTu4JPeFxmwmaKOJG_E5_Cl6cvUYNVV-LhWOjMurJSWiAoUo4GN1_TiZfu1JUORPajK2oA4rSJOewak7UqwVDkP9-pSOkpPxfoanQCEIwRiwkmtvJC74Kpw24ckrBu2tgNZLxeyKkGcZmWPLmh6AxKGgJ1yhnDzzKWleJ7cyM_80ORbBjCTCnldmaoRJygkUdZIblsYSQgG7w;
        Domain=.eventbrite.com; httponly; Path=/
      - SS=AE3DLHQy0UxDEY9tQMjB2gUbEuxKS9GDYA; Domain=.eventbrite.com; httponly; Path=/;
        secure
      - eblang=lo%3Den_US%26la%3Den-us; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015
        15:16:50 GMT; httponly; Path=/
      - mgref=typeins; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:16:50 GMT;
        httponly; Max-Age=31536000; Path=/
      - mgrefby=; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:16:50 GMT; httponly;
        Max-Age=31536000; Path=/
      Transfer-Enc<METRICS_API_USERNAME>ng:
      - chunked
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ! '{"error": {"error_type": "Not Found", "error_message": "No records
        were found with the given parameters."}}'
    http_version: 
  recorded_at: Thu, 07 Aug 2014 15:16:58 GMT
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://www.eventbrite.com/json/event_list_attendees?app_key=<EVENTBRITE_API_KEY>&id=5441375300&page=0&user_key=<EVENTBRITE_USER_KEY>
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers: {}
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Server:
      - nginx
      Date:
      - Thu, 07 Aug 2014 15:46:54 GMT
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
      Connection:
      - keep-alive
      X-Xss-Protection:
      - 1; mode=block
      X-Content-Type-Options:
      - nosniff
      Expires:
      - Fri, 01 Jan 1990 00:00:00 GMT
      Vary:
      - Accept-Enc<METRICS_API_USERNAME>ng
      X-Service:
      - djc
      X-Ua-Compatible:
      - IE=edge
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Cache-Control:
      - no-cache, must-revalidate, no-cache="Set-Cookie", private
      P3p:
      - CP="NOI ADM DEV PSAi COM NAV OUR OTRo STP IND DEM"
      X-Frame-Options:
      - SAMEORIGIN
      Set-Cookie:
      - AN=; expires=Thu, 01-Jan-1970 00:00:00 GMT; Max-Age=0; Path=/
      - G=v%3D1%26i%3Dcd3e09fc-1598-4e92-a342-996eb7e189b3%26a%3D4aa%26s%3DAPDvTK54KOl-AEZ5rmbe9D_DGD-R05CFQQ;
        Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:46:54 GMT; httponly; Path=/
      - SP=AGQgbbmuzc6g-MrNmXXI7Imaw_Kco6XJqestmylTxoRNdRhN1jm3vqzdp5M1cr-7w9ayLpwRvXuqBuyOujAtz42CNLkv0iltI63KMzyyL_pzVomBVGqEt67G2Un6qm4CloovQhaMnNlxb_6HcN7w2xtopk19NsdQ8zhf-sb2aniL-PBiHJY2_4SZi0zonfD9GB6DtlX_f-MxGvjvHQzp4FG74k6RuyhrWsk3ub1YdQJSN35tQJa6hss;
        Domain=.eventbrite.com; httponly; Path=/
      - SS=AE3DLHQCAgCGxrgi3Tsgxr5CAwbvq4v4UQ; Domain=.eventbrite.com; httponly; Path=/;
        secure
      - eblang=lo%3Den_US%26la%3Den-us; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015
        15:46:54 GMT; httponly; Path=/
      - mgref=typeins; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:46:54 GMT;
        httponly; Max-Age=31536000; Path=/
      - mgrefby=; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:46:54 GMT; httponly;
        Max-Age=31536000; Path=/
      Transfer-Enc<METRICS_API_USERNAME>ng:
      - chunked
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ! '{"attendees": [{"attendee": {"ticket_id": 17042456, "last_name":
        "Fish", "suffix": "", "ship_region": "Berkshire", "ship_country": "GB", "tax":
        "0.20", "currency": "GBP", "prefix": "", "id": 181778454, "first_name": "Bob",
        "order_type": "Send an Invoice - Payment Not Received", "event_id": 5441375300,
        "blog": "", "email": "bob.fish@example.com", "notes": "", "event_date": "",
        "eventbrite_fee": "0.68", "amount_paid": "1.20", "job_title": "", "website":
        "", "ship_address": "29 Acacia Road", "ship_country_code": "GB", "order_id":
        142052968, "company": "New Company Inc.", "barcode": "142052968181778454001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "123 Random Business Park", "question":
        "Billing Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "The Rough End", "question": "Billing Address (line
        2)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518668}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "London", "question": "Billing Address (city)", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "Greater London", "question": "Billing
        Address (region)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518684}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "UK", "question": "Billing Address (country)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518686}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "EC1A 1AA", "question":
        "Billing Address (postcode)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518688}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "finance@newcompany.com", "question": "Billing
        Email", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493382}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "01234 5678910", "question": "Billing Phone Number", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB5678", "question":
        "VAT reg number (if non-UK)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493390}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "9101112", "question": "Membership Number", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB1234", "question":
        "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518878}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "Public sector", "question": "Sector", "question_type":
        "multiple choice", "question_id": 7188287}}], "discount": "", "created": "2013-02-15
        01:20:27", "ship_postal_code": "NT4 3HG", "gender": "", "ship_address_2":
        "The Posh End", "m<METRICS_API_USERNAME>fied": "2014-05-30 05:55:09", "cc_fee":
        "0.00", "affiliate": "", "ship_phone": "", "ship_city": "Dandytown", "birth_date":
        "", "cell_phone": "01234 098765", "age": "", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee":
        {"ticket_id": 17042456, "last_name": "Fish", "suffix": "", "ship_region":
        "Berkshire", "ship_country": "GB", "tax": "0.20", "currency": "GBP", "prefix":
        "", "id": 181778452, "first_name": "Bob", "order_type": "Send an Invoice -
        Payment Not Received", "event_id": 5441375300, "blog": "", "email": "bob.fish@example.com",
        "notes": "", "event_date": "", "eventbrite_fee": "0.68", "amount_paid": "1.20",
        "job_title": "", "website": "", "ship_address": "29 Acacia Road", "ship_country_code":
        "GB", "order_id": 142052968, "company": "New Company Inc.", "barcode": "142052968181778452001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "123 Random Business Park", "question":
        "Billing Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "The Rough End", "question": "Billing Address (line
        2)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518668}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "London", "question": "Billing Address (city)", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "Greater London", "question": "Billing
        Address (region)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518684}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "UK", "question": "Billing Address (country)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518686}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "EC1A 1AA", "question":
        "Billing Address (postcode)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518688}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "finance@newcompany.com", "question": "Billing
        Email", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493382}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "01234 5678910", "question": "Billing Phone Number", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB5678", "question":
        "VAT reg number (if non-UK)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493390}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "9101112", "question": "Membership Number", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB1234", "question":
        "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518878}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "Public sector", "question": "Sector", "question_type":
        "multiple choice", "question_id": 7188287}}], "discount": "", "created": "2013-02-15
        01:20:27", "ship_postal_code": "NT4 3HG", "gender": "", "ship_address_2":
        "The Posh End", "m<METRICS_API_USERNAME>fied": "2014-05-30 05:39:54", "cc_fee":
        "0.00", "affiliate": "", "ship_phone": "", "ship_city": "Dandytown", "birth_date":
        "", "cell_phone": "01234 098765", "age": "", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee":
        {"last_name": "Fish", "ship_region": "", "ship_country": "GB", "tax": "0.00",
        "currency": "GBP", "id": 181781836, "first_name": "Bob", "order_type": "Free
        Order", "event_id": 5441375300, "ticket_id": 17042304, "event_date": "", "eventbrite_fee":
        "0.00", "email": "bob.fish@example.com", "ship_address": "", "ship_country_code":
        "GB", "order_id": 142055824, "amount_paid": "0.00", "barcode": "142055824181781836001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "Public sector", "question": "Sector",
        "question_type": "multiple choice", "question_id": 7188287}}], "discount":
        "", "created": "2013-02-15 01:49:13", "ship_postal_code": "", "ship_city":
        "", "ship_address_2": "", "m<METRICS_API_USERNAME>fied": "2014-05-30 05:41:32",
        "affiliate": "", "ship_phone": "", "cc_fee": "0.00", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee":
        {"ticket_id": 17042456, "last_name": "Fish", "suffix": "", "ship_region":
        "Berkshire", "ship_country": "GB", "tax": "0.20", "currency": "GBP", "prefix":
        "", "id": 181785692, "first_name": "Bob", "order_type": "PayPal Completed",
        "event_id": 5441375300, "blog": "", "email": "bob.fish@example.com", "notes":
        "", "event_date": "", "eventbrite_fee": "0.68", "amount_paid": "1.20", "job_title":
        "", "website": "", "ship_address": "29 Acacia Road", "ship_country_code":
        "GB", "order_id": 142059188, "company": "New Company Inc.", "barcode": "142059188181785692001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "123 Random Business Park", "question":
        "Billing Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "The Rough End", "question": "Billing Address (line
        2)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518668}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "London", "question": "Billing Address (city)", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "Greater London", "question": "Billing
        Address (region)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518684}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "UK", "question": "Billing Address (country)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518686}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "EC1A 1AA", "question":
        "Billing Address (postcode)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518688}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "finance@newcompany.com", "question": "Billing
        Email", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493382}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "01234 5678910", "question": "Billing Phone Number", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB5678", "question":
        "VAT reg number (if non-UK)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493390}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "9101112", "question": "Membership Number", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB1234", "question":
        "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518878}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "Public sector", "question": "Sector", "question_type":
        "multiple choice", "question_id": 7188287}}], "discount": "", "created": "2013-02-15
        02:20:48", "ship_postal_code": "NT4 3HG", "gender": "", "ship_address_2":
        "The Posh End", "m<METRICS_API_USERNAME>fied": "2014-05-30 05:41:47", "cc_fee":
        "0.00", "affiliate": "", "ship_phone": "", "ship_city": "Dandytown", "birth_date":
        "", "cell_phone": "01234 098765", "age": "", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee":
        {"ticket_id": 17042456, "last_name": "Miliband", "suffix": "", "ship_region":
        "West Sussex", "ship_country": "GB", "tax": "0.20", "currency": "GBP", "prefix":
        "", "id": 187690446, "first_name": "Ed", "order_type": "Send an Invoice -
        Payment Not Received", "event_id": 5441375300, "blog": "", "email": "ed@example.com",
        "notes": "", "event_date": "", "eventbrite_fee": "0.68", "amount_paid": "1.20",
        "job_title": "", "website": "", "ship_address": "14 Greenfinch Way", "ship_country_code":
        "GB", "order_id": 146845618, "company": "Labour Party", "barcode": "146845618187690446001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "14 Greenfinch Way", "question": "Billing
        Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "Horsham", "question": "Billing Address (city)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "UK", "question":
        "Billing Address (country)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518686}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "RH12 5HB", "question": "Billing Address (postcode)",
        "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518688}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "james+finance@floppy.org.uk", "question": "Billing Email", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493382}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "07715 432435",
        "question": "Billing Phone Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB1234YZ", "question": "Membership
        Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "PO1234666454", "question": "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3518878}}], "discount": "", "created": "2013-03-01 01:04:32",
        "ship_postal_code": "RH12 5HB", "gender": "", "ship_address_2": "", "m<METRICS_API_USERNAME>fied":
        "2013-07-24 02:18:15", "cc_fee": "0.00", "affiliate": "", "ship_phone": "",
        "ship_city": "Horsham", "birth_date": "", "cell_phone": "+44 1735 324312",
        "age": "", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee": {"last_name": "Smith", "ship_region":
        "", "ship_country": "GB", "tax": "0.20", "currency": "GBP", "id": 182609582,
        "first_name": "James", "order_type": "Send an Invoice - Payment Not Received",
        "event_id": 5441375300, "ticket_id": 17042456, "event_date": "", "eventbrite_fee":
        "0.68", "email": "james@floppy.org.uk", "ship_address": "", "ship_country_code":
        "GB", "order_id": 142722298, "amount_paid": "1.20", "barcode": "142722298182609582001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "14 Greenfinch Way", "question": "Billing
        Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "Horsham", "question": "Billing Address (city)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "West Sussex",
        "question": "Billing Address (region)", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518684}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "UK", "question": "Billing Address (country)",
        "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518686}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "RH12 5HB", "question": "Billing Address (postcode)", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3518688}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "james@floppy.org.uk",
        "question": "Billing Email", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493382}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "07715 105349", "question": "Billing Phone Number",
        "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "XX121342543", "question": "Membership Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "PO123442", "question": "Purchase Order
        Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518878}}], "discount": "",
        "created": "2013-02-18 01:25:48", "ship_postal_code": "", "ship_city": "",
        "ship_address_2": "", "m<METRICS_API_USERNAME>fied": "2013-07-24 02:18:16",
        "affiliate": "", "ship_phone": "", "cc_fee": "0.00", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee":
        {"ticket_id": 17042456, "last_name": "Smith", "suffix": "", "ship_region":
        "West Sussex", "ship_country": "GB", "tax": "0.20", "currency": "GBP", "prefix":
        "", "id": 182620900, "first_name": "James", "order_type": "Send an Invoice
        - Payment Not Received", "event_id": 5441375300, "blog": "", "email": "james@floppy.org.uk",
        "notes": "", "event_date": "", "eventbrite_fee": "0.68", "amount_paid": "1.20",
        "job_title": "", "website": "", "ship_address": "14 Greenfinch Way", "ship_country_code":
        "GB", "order_id": 142731672, "company": "Widgets ''r'' us", "barcode": "142731672182620900001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "14 Greenfinch Way", "question": "Billing
        Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "Horsham", "question": "Billing Address (city)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "UK", "question":
        "Billing Address (country)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518686}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "RH12 5HB", "question": "Billing Address (postcode)",
        "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518688}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "james+finance@floppy.org.uk", "question": "Billing Email", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493382}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "07715 154387",
        "question": "Billing Phone Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "ODI45434", "question": "Membership
        Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "PO453543", "question": "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3518878}}], "discount": "", "created": "2013-02-18 02:51:44",
        "ship_postal_code": "RH12 5HB", "gender": "", "ship_address_2": "", "m<METRICS_API_USERNAME>fied":
        "2013-02-18 02:54:32", "cc_fee": "0.00", "affiliate": "", "ship_phone": "",
        "ship_city": "Horsham", "birth_date": "", "cell_phone": "07715105349", "age":
        "", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee": {"ticket_id": 17042456, "last_name": "Smith",
        "suffix": "", "ship_region": "West Sussex", "ship_country": "GB", "tax": "0.20",
        "currency": "GBP", "prefix": "", "id": 181804062, "first_name": "James", "order_type":
        "Send an Invoice - Payment Not Received", "event_id": 5441375300, "blog":
        "", "email": "james@floppy.org.uk", "notes": "", "event_date": "", "eventbrite_fee":
        "0.68", "amount_paid": "1.20", "job_title": "", "website": "", "ship_address":
        "14 Greenfinch Way", "ship_country_code": "GB", "order_id": 142074438, "company":
        "The ODI", "barcode": "142074438181804062001", "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text":
        "65 Clifton Street", "question": "Billing Address (line 1)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493380}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "-", "question":
        "Billing Address (line 2)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518668}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "London", "question": "Billing Address (city)",
        "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "-", "question": "Billing Address (region)", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518684}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "UK", "question": "Billing Address (country)",
        "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518686}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "No idea", "question": "Billing Address (postcode)", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3518688}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "james+billing@floppy.org.uk",
        "question": "Billing Email", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493382}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "07715 105349", "question": "Billing Phone Number",
        "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "123243", "question": "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518878}}], "discount": "", "created": "2013-02-15 04:34:29", "ship_postal_code":
        "RH12 5HB", "gender": "", "ship_address_2": "", "m<METRICS_API_USERNAME>fied":
        "2013-02-15 04:35:57", "cc_fee": "0.00", "affiliate": "", "ship_phone": "",
        "ship_city": "Horsham", "birth_date": "", "cell_phone": "07715105349", "age":
        "", "quantity": 1}}]}'
    http_version: 
  recorded_at: Thu, 07 Aug 2014 15:47:03 GMT
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://www.eventbrite.com/json/event_get?app_key=<EVENTBRITE_API_KEY>&id=5441375300&user_key=<EVENTBRITE_USER_KEY>
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers: {}
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Server:
      - nginx
      Date:
      - Thu, 07 Aug 2014 15:46:59 GMT
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
      Connection:
      - keep-alive
      X-Xss-Protection:
      - 1; mode=block
      X-Content-Type-Options:
      - nosniff
      Expires:
      - Fri, 01 Jan 1990 00:00:00 GMT
      Vary:
      - Accept-Enc<METRICS_API_USERNAME>ng
      X-Service:
      - djc
      X-Ua-Compatible:
      - IE=edge
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Cache-Control:
      - no-cache, must-revalidate, no-cache="Set-Cookie", private
      P3p:
      - CP="NOI ADM DEV PSAi COM NAV OUR OTRo STP IND DEM"
      X-Frame-Options:
      - SAMEORIGIN
      Set-Cookie:
      - AN=; expires=Thu, 01-Jan-1970 00:00:00 GMT; Max-Age=0; Path=/
      - G=v%3D1%26i%3De8c927f7-5ecf-43f9-9521-a65bc7b38501%26a%3D4aa%26s%3DAPDvTK5J3gQkolTXtz0B8j77Pu0cb5eJvA;
        Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:46:59 GMT; httponly; Path=/
      - SP=AGQgbbn7kE-pVr7QyFBDk7GYa5IAwPsAp2piOgYlGONK9gYNWWWEnZFWVHtB8WhFSCqwOd2ZBtKWQOW0X1m9urm9aodYrqOHJ1prlQy2u7T0GBpRVpJL2eyDB9G4iOoeMkpHPNiiANgBYxEvnKd3JGFcNUTcwctoW_j0XQqI_pkexYWxWec6k8A2_I--lHDtd8aXThmXwAgRMosoHciG5dapfCZfCFoYLTqUKXRlRBLdhfLDgqMbfRM;
        Domain=.eventbrite.com; httponly; Path=/
      - SS=AE3DLHRIrSte8BkqZckCYZPHC0_o6P21YA; Domain=.eventbrite.com; httponly; Path=/;
        secure
      - eblang=lo%3Den_US%26la%3Den-us; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015
        15:46:59 GMT; httponly; Path=/
      - mgref=typeins; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:46:59 GMT;
        httponly; Max-Age=31536000; Path=/
      - mgrefby=; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:46:59 GMT; httponly;
        Max-Age=31536000; Path=/
      Transfer-Enc<METRICS_API_USERNAME>ng:
      - chunked
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ! '{"event": {"box_header_text_color": "005580", "locale": "en_GB",
        "link_color": "EE6600", "box_background_color": "FFFFFF", "box_border_color":
        "D5D5D3", "timezone": "Europe/London", "organizer": {"url": "http://www.eventbrite.co.uk/o/<METRICS_API_USERNAME>-tech-<EVENTBRITE_ORGANIZER_ID>",
        "description": "", "long_description": "Just here for the testing...", "id":
        <EVENTBRITE_ORGANIZER_ID>, "name": "ODI Tech"}, "background_color": "FFFFFF",
        "id": 5441375300, "category": "", "box_header_background_color": "EFEFEF",
        "capacity": 0, "num_attendee_rows": 8.0, "title": "[Test Event 00] Drupal:
        Down the Rabbit Hole", "start_date": "2013-06-17 19:00:00", "status": "Completed",
        "description": "<P>This is the description.</P>", "end_date": "2013-06-17
        22:00:00", "tags": "", "timezone_offset": "GMT+0100", "text_color": "005580",
        "title_text_color": "", "password": "", "tickets": [{"ticket": {"description":
        "", "end_date": "2013-06-17 18:00:00", "min": 1, "max": null, "price": "0.00",
        "quantity_sold": 1, "visible": "true", "start_date": "2013-02-11 09:00:00",
        "currency": "GBP", "quantity_available": 100, "display_price": "0.00", "type":
        0, "id": 17042304, "include_fee": "true", "name": "Free Ticket"}}, {"ticket":
        {"description": "", "end_date": "2013-06-17 18:00:00", "min": 1, "max": null,
        "price": "1.00", "quantity_sold": 7, "visible": "true", "currency": "GBP",
        "quantity_available": 100, "display_price": "1.00", "type": 0, "id": 17042456,
        "include_fee": "true", "name": "Cheap Ticket"}}], "created": "2013-02-05 09:08:12",
        "url": "https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/test-event-00-drupal-down-the-rabbit-hole-tickets-5441375300?ref=ebapi",
        "box_text_color": "000000", "privacy": "Private", "venue": {"city": "", "name":
        "The office", "country": "", "region": "", "longitude": 0.0, "postal_code":
        "", "address_2": "", "address": "", "latitude": 0.0, "country_code": "", "id":
        2959410, "Lat-Long": "0.0 / 0.0"}, "m<METRICS_API_USERNAME>fied": "2014-05-30
        05:38:28", "repeats": "no"}}'
    http_version: 
  recorded_at: Thu, 07 Aug 2014 15:47:07 GMT
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://www.eventbrite.com/json/event_list_attendees?app_key=<EVENTBRITE_API_KEY>&id=5441375300&page=0&user_key=<EVENTBRITE_USER_KEY>
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers: {}
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Server:
      - nginx
      Date:
      - Thu, 07 Aug 2014 15:47:39 GMT
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
      Connection:
      - keep-alive
      X-Xss-Protection:
      - 1; mode=block
      X-Content-Type-Options:
      - nosniff
      Expires:
      - Fri, 01 Jan 1990 00:00:00 GMT
      Vary:
      - Accept-Enc<METRICS_API_USERNAME>ng
      X-Service:
      - djc
      X-Ua-Compatible:
      - IE=edge
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Cache-Control:
      - no-cache, must-revalidate, no-cache="Set-Cookie", private
      P3p:
      - CP="NOI ADM DEV PSAi COM NAV OUR OTRo STP IND DEM"
      X-Frame-Options:
      - SAMEORIGIN
      Set-Cookie:
      - AN=; expires=Thu, 01-Jan-1970 00:00:00 GMT; Max-Age=0; Path=/
      - G=v%3D1%26i%3D3afe8a0c-061a-4388-9ddd-1bccd04b5216%26a%3D4aa%26s%3DAPDvTK7X6ldVGtDnk4cwN8ekgBgZu2pdIQ;
        Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:47:39 GMT; httponly; Path=/
      - SP=AGQgbbnUV8xfZrPZ1Qn5aHU1K8Cyvpir1VYqY9hu8kbWGWZA3EtfF2bchzjTUmGoS1TUmKl9O8Z3SOELAggg_KzfWLk_O63lDOvNGHLFWdwpVwkDVjDnsyb7nsgssAgeXULhDmmxJzfgbnKAnGibgpMjJFto_X97Ydp-02OXsfAwYTaEm4mx98inDTkEnBxyDD-5xrBg0Zv9wf4JGneVt11Z2ZPCa2nTEtI8mXlbZ03NaqMx_GBLEK8;
        Domain=.eventbrite.com; httponly; Path=/
      - SS=AE3DLHQ5aPb4Ldt_-pm7RWcIMgWI3gyGpA; Domain=.eventbrite.com; httponly; Path=/;
        secure
      - eblang=lo%3Den_US%26la%3Den-us; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015
        15:47:39 GMT; httponly; Path=/
      - mgref=typeins; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:47:39 GMT;
        httponly; Max-Age=31536000; Path=/
      - mgrefby=; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:47:39 GMT; httponly;
        Max-Age=31536000; Path=/
      Transfer-Enc<METRICS_API_USERNAME>ng:
      - chunked
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ! '{"attendees": [{"attendee": {"ticket_id": 17042456, "last_name":
        "Fish", "suffix": "", "ship_region": "Berkshire", "ship_country": "GB", "tax":
        "0.20", "currency": "GBP", "prefix": "", "id": 181778454, "first_name": "Bob",
        "order_type": "Send an Invoice - Payment Not Received", "event_id": 5441375300,
        "blog": "", "email": "bob.fish@example.com", "notes": "", "event_date": "",
        "eventbrite_fee": "0.68", "amount_paid": "1.20", "job_title": "", "website":
        "", "ship_address": "29 Acacia Road", "ship_country_code": "GB", "order_id":
        142052968, "company": "New Company Inc.", "barcode": "142052968181778454001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "123 Random Business Park", "question":
        "Billing Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "The Rough End", "question": "Billing Address (line
        2)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518668}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "London", "question": "Billing Address (city)", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "Greater London", "question": "Billing
        Address (region)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518684}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "UK", "question": "Billing Address (country)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518686}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "EC1A 1AA", "question":
        "Billing Address (postcode)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518688}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "finance@newcompany.com", "question": "Billing
        Email", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493382}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "01234 5678910", "question": "Billing Phone Number", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB5678", "question":
        "VAT reg number (if non-UK)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493390}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "9101112", "question": "Membership Number", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB1234", "question":
        "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518878}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "Public sector", "question": "Sector", "question_type":
        "multiple choice", "question_id": 7188287}}], "discount": "", "created": "2013-02-15
        01:20:27", "ship_postal_code": "NT4 3HG", "gender": "", "ship_address_2":
        "The Posh End", "m<METRICS_API_USERNAME>fied": "2014-05-30 05:55:09", "cc_fee":
        "0.00", "affiliate": "", "ship_phone": "", "ship_city": "Dandytown", "birth_date":
        "", "cell_phone": "01234 098765", "age": "", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee":
        {"ticket_id": 17042456, "last_name": "Fish", "suffix": "", "ship_region":
        "Berkshire", "ship_country": "GB", "tax": "0.20", "currency": "GBP", "prefix":
        "", "id": 181778452, "first_name": "Bob", "order_type": "Send an Invoice -
        Payment Not Received", "event_id": 5441375300, "blog": "", "email": "bob.fish@example.com",
        "notes": "", "event_date": "", "eventbrite_fee": "0.68", "amount_paid": "1.20",
        "job_title": "", "website": "", "ship_address": "29 Acacia Road", "ship_country_code":
        "GB", "order_id": 142052968, "company": "New Company Inc.", "barcode": "142052968181778452001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "123 Random Business Park", "question":
        "Billing Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "The Rough End", "question": "Billing Address (line
        2)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518668}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "London", "question": "Billing Address (city)", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "Greater London", "question": "Billing
        Address (region)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518684}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "UK", "question": "Billing Address (country)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518686}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "EC1A 1AA", "question":
        "Billing Address (postcode)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518688}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "finance@newcompany.com", "question": "Billing
        Email", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493382}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "01234 5678910", "question": "Billing Phone Number", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB5678", "question":
        "VAT reg number (if non-UK)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493390}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "9101112", "question": "Membership Number", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB1234", "question":
        "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518878}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "Public sector", "question": "Sector", "question_type":
        "multiple choice", "question_id": 7188287}}], "discount": "", "created": "2013-02-15
        01:20:27", "ship_postal_code": "NT4 3HG", "gender": "", "ship_address_2":
        "The Posh End", "m<METRICS_API_USERNAME>fied": "2014-05-30 05:39:54", "cc_fee":
        "0.00", "affiliate": "", "ship_phone": "", "ship_city": "Dandytown", "birth_date":
        "", "cell_phone": "01234 098765", "age": "", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee":
        {"last_name": "Fish", "ship_region": "", "ship_country": "GB", "tax": "0.00",
        "currency": "GBP", "id": 181781836, "first_name": "Bob", "order_type": "Free
        Order", "event_id": 5441375300, "ticket_id": 17042304, "event_date": "", "eventbrite_fee":
        "0.00", "email": "bob.fish@example.com", "ship_address": "", "ship_country_code":
        "GB", "order_id": 142055824, "amount_paid": "0.00", "barcode": "142055824181781836001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "Public sector", "question": "Sector",
        "question_type": "multiple choice", "question_id": 7188287}}], "discount":
        "", "created": "2013-02-15 01:49:13", "ship_postal_code": "", "ship_city":
        "", "ship_address_2": "", "m<METRICS_API_USERNAME>fied": "2014-05-30 05:41:32",
        "affiliate": "", "ship_phone": "", "cc_fee": "0.00", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee":
        {"ticket_id": 17042456, "last_name": "Fish", "suffix": "", "ship_region":
        "Berkshire", "ship_country": "GB", "tax": "0.20", "currency": "GBP", "prefix":
        "", "id": 181785692, "first_name": "Bob", "order_type": "PayPal Completed",
        "event_id": 5441375300, "blog": "", "email": "bob.fish@example.com", "notes":
        "", "event_date": "", "eventbrite_fee": "0.68", "amount_paid": "1.20", "job_title":
        "", "website": "", "ship_address": "29 Acacia Road", "ship_country_code":
        "GB", "order_id": 142059188, "company": "New Company Inc.", "barcode": "142059188181785692001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "123 Random Business Park", "question":
        "Billing Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "The Rough End", "question": "Billing Address (line
        2)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518668}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "London", "question": "Billing Address (city)", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "Greater London", "question": "Billing
        Address (region)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518684}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "UK", "question": "Billing Address (country)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518686}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "EC1A 1AA", "question":
        "Billing Address (postcode)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518688}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "finance@newcompany.com", "question": "Billing
        Email", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493382}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "01234 5678910", "question": "Billing Phone Number", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB5678", "question":
        "VAT reg number (if non-UK)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493390}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "9101112", "question": "Membership Number", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB1234", "question":
        "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518878}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "Public sector", "question": "Sector", "question_type":
        "multiple choice", "question_id": 7188287}}], "discount": "", "created": "2013-02-15
        02:20:48", "ship_postal_code": "NT4 3HG", "gender": "", "ship_address_2":
        "The Posh End", "m<METRICS_API_USERNAME>fied": "2014-05-30 05:41:47", "cc_fee":
        "0.00", "affiliate": "", "ship_phone": "", "ship_city": "Dandytown", "birth_date":
        "", "cell_phone": "01234 098765", "age": "", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee":
        {"ticket_id": 17042456, "last_name": "Miliband", "suffix": "", "ship_region":
        "West Sussex", "ship_country": "GB", "tax": "0.20", "currency": "GBP", "prefix":
        "", "id": 187690446, "first_name": "Ed", "order_type": "Send an Invoice -
        Payment Not Received", "event_id": 5441375300, "blog": "", "email": "ed@example.com",
        "notes": "", "event_date": "", "eventbrite_fee": "0.68", "amount_paid": "1.20",
        "job_title": "", "website": "", "ship_address": "14 Greenfinch Way", "ship_country_code":
        "GB", "order_id": 146845618, "company": "Labour Party", "barcode": "146845618187690446001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "14 Greenfinch Way", "question": "Billing
        Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "Horsham", "question": "Billing Address (city)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "UK", "question":
        "Billing Address (country)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518686}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "RH12 5HB", "question": "Billing Address (postcode)",
        "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518688}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "james+finance@floppy.org.uk", "question": "Billing Email", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493382}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "07715 432435",
        "question": "Billing Phone Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "AB1234YZ", "question": "Membership
        Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "PO1234666454", "question": "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3518878}}], "discount": "", "created": "2013-03-01 01:04:32",
        "ship_postal_code": "RH12 5HB", "gender": "", "ship_address_2": "", "m<METRICS_API_USERNAME>fied":
        "2013-07-24 02:18:15", "cc_fee": "0.00", "affiliate": "", "ship_phone": "",
        "ship_city": "Horsham", "birth_date": "", "cell_phone": "+44 1735 324312",
        "age": "", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee": {"ticket_id": 17042456, "last_name":
        "Smith", "suffix": "", "ship_region": "West Sussex", "ship_country": "GB",
        "tax": "0.20", "currency": "GBP", "prefix": "", "id": 181804062, "first_name":
        "James", "order_type": "Send an Invoice - Payment Not Received", "event_id":
        5441375300, "blog": "", "email": "james@floppy.org.uk", "notes": "", "event_date":
        "", "eventbrite_fee": "0.68", "amount_paid": "1.20", "job_title": "", "website":
        "", "ship_address": "14 Greenfinch Way", "ship_country_code": "GB", "order_id":
        142074438, "company": "The ODI", "barcode": "142074438181804062001", "answers":
        [{"answer": {"answer_text": "65 Clifton Street", "question": "Billing Address
        (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "-", "question": "Billing Address (line 2)", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518668}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "London", "question": "Billing Address
        (city)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "-", "question": "Billing Address (region)", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518684}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "UK", "question": "Billing Address (country)",
        "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518686}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "No idea", "question": "Billing Address (postcode)", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3518688}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "james+billing@floppy.org.uk",
        "question": "Billing Email", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493382}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "07715 105349", "question": "Billing Phone Number",
        "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "123243", "question": "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518878}}], "discount": "", "created": "2013-02-15 04:34:29", "ship_postal_code":
        "RH12 5HB", "gender": "", "ship_address_2": "", "m<METRICS_API_USERNAME>fied":
        "2013-02-15 04:35:57", "cc_fee": "0.00", "affiliate": "", "ship_phone": "",
        "ship_city": "Horsham", "birth_date": "", "cell_phone": "07715105349", "age":
        "", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee": {"last_name": "Smith", "ship_region": "",
        "ship_country": "GB", "tax": "0.20", "currency": "GBP", "id": 182609582, "first_name":
        "James", "order_type": "Send an Invoice - Payment Not Received", "event_id":
        5441375300, "ticket_id": 17042456, "event_date": "", "eventbrite_fee": "0.68",
        "email": "james@floppy.org.uk", "ship_address": "", "ship_country_code": "GB",
        "order_id": 142722298, "amount_paid": "1.20", "barcode": "142722298182609582001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "14 Greenfinch Way", "question": "Billing
        Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "Horsham", "question": "Billing Address (city)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "West Sussex",
        "question": "Billing Address (region)", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3518684}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "UK", "question": "Billing Address (country)",
        "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518686}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "RH12 5HB", "question": "Billing Address (postcode)", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3518688}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "james@floppy.org.uk",
        "question": "Billing Email", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493382}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "07715 105349", "question": "Billing Phone Number",
        "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "XX121342543", "question": "Membership Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "PO123442", "question": "Purchase Order
        Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518878}}], "discount": "",
        "created": "2013-02-18 01:25:48", "ship_postal_code": "", "ship_city": "",
        "ship_address_2": "", "m<METRICS_API_USERNAME>fied": "2013-07-24 02:18:16",
        "affiliate": "", "ship_phone": "", "cc_fee": "0.00", "quantity": 1}}, {"attendee":
        {"ticket_id": 17042456, "last_name": "Smith", "suffix": "", "ship_region":
        "West Sussex", "ship_country": "GB", "tax": "0.20", "currency": "GBP", "prefix":
        "", "id": 182620900, "first_name": "James", "order_type": "Send an Invoice
        - Payment Not Received", "event_id": 5441375300, "blog": "", "email": "james@floppy.org.uk",
        "notes": "", "event_date": "", "eventbrite_fee": "0.68", "amount_paid": "1.20",
        "job_title": "", "website": "", "ship_address": "14 Greenfinch Way", "ship_country_code":
        "GB", "order_id": 142731672, "company": "Widgets ''r'' us", "barcode": "142731672182620900001",
        "answers": [{"answer": {"answer_text": "14 Greenfinch Way", "question": "Billing
        Address (line 1)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493380}}, {"answer":
        {"answer_text": "Horsham", "question": "Billing Address (city)", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3518682}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "UK", "question":
        "Billing Address (country)", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518686}},
        {"answer": {"answer_text": "RH12 5HB", "question": "Billing Address (postcode)",
        "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3518688}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "james+finance@floppy.org.uk", "question": "Billing Email", "question_type":
        "text", "question_id": 3493382}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "07715 154387",
        "question": "Billing Phone Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id":
        3493384}}, {"answer": {"answer_text": "ODI45434", "question": "Membership
        Number", "question_type": "text", "question_id": 3493388}}, {"answer": {"answer_text":
        "PO453543", "question": "Purchase Order Number", "question_type": "text",
        "question_id": 3518878}}], "discount": "", "created": "2013-02-18 02:51:44",
        "ship_postal_code": "RH12 5HB", "gender": "", "ship_address_2": "", "m<METRICS_API_USERNAME>fied":
        "2013-02-18 02:54:32", "cc_fee": "0.00", "affiliate": "", "ship_phone": "",
        "ship_city": "Horsham", "birth_date": "", "cell_phone": "07715105349", "age":
        "", "quantity": 1}}]}'
    http_version: 
  recorded_at: Thu, 07 Aug 2014 15:47:48 GMT
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://www.eventbrite.com/json/event_get?app_key=<EVENTBRITE_API_KEY>&id=5441375300&user_key=<EVENTBRITE_USER_KEY>
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers: {}
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Server:
      - nginx
      Date:
      - Thu, 07 Aug 2014 15:47:42 GMT
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
      Connection:
      - keep-alive
      X-Xss-Protection:
      - 1; mode=block
      X-Content-Type-Options:
      - nosniff
      Expires:
      - Fri, 01 Jan 1990 00:00:00 GMT
      Vary:
      - Accept-Enc<METRICS_API_USERNAME>ng
      X-Service:
      - djc
      X-Ua-Compatible:
      - IE=edge
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Cache-Control:
      - no-cache, must-revalidate, no-cache="Set-Cookie", private
      P3p:
      - CP="NOI ADM DEV PSAi COM NAV OUR OTRo STP IND DEM"
      X-Frame-Options:
      - SAMEORIGIN
      Set-Cookie:
      - AN=; expires=Thu, 01-Jan-1970 00:00:00 GMT; Max-Age=0; Path=/
      - G=v%3D1%26i%3Dd792c569-3aac-403d-b8e7-ad669a5aa84f%26a%3D4aa%26s%3DAPDvTK6YfIyCWKcW0Y9Ynn1z9VGD4UGwTA;
        Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:47:42 GMT; httponly; Path=/
      - SP=AGQgbbn6NUCYfcbunVwqBjI4F9XKxNch3LEn0xHsWcIDTi5bThjmH9eNv9T9KUyxnDC2pNMnV64D_sspz1nWp7XvvE1gdh_RxQ8Fxq2AiAsnjSNpPrWWN-eNLcjyvwU1RUyeo7Nrb0M3uXWSZHimOyebqwF94urlkbU81asSyP9d7b0XUtGNzIOICwquPpC5Sh7DICsQM90JVtXUao7DFD9vQyoc8jlRUWwBT9V7lPDwApgPKy-jRk4;
        Domain=.eventbrite.com; httponly; Path=/
      - SS=AE3DLHSpdkFp9yzGVcGOn7Na0fST3bckhg; Domain=.eventbrite.com; httponly; Path=/;
        secure
      - eblang=lo%3Den_US%26la%3Den-us; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015
        15:47:42 GMT; httponly; Path=/
      - mgref=typeins; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:47:42 GMT;
        httponly; Max-Age=31536000; Path=/
      - mgrefby=; Domain=.eventbrite.com; expires=Fri, 07-Aug-2015 15:47:42 GMT; httponly;
        Max-Age=31536000; Path=/
      Transfer-Enc<METRICS_API_USERNAME>ng:
      - chunked
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ! '{"event": {"box_header_text_color": "005580", "locale": "en_GB",
        "link_color": "EE6600", "box_background_color": "FFFFFF", "box_border_color":
        "D5D5D3", "timezone": "Europe/London", "organizer": {"url": "http://www.eventbrite.co.uk/o/<METRICS_API_USERNAME>-tech-<EVENTBRITE_ORGANIZER_ID>",
        "description": "", "long_description": "Just here for the testing...", "id":
        <EVENTBRITE_ORGANIZER_ID>, "name": "ODI Tech"}, "background_color": "FFFFFF",
        "id": 5441375300, "category": "", "box_header_background_color": "EFEFEF",
        "capacity": 0, "num_attendee_rows": 8.0, "title": "[Test Event 00] Drupal:
        Down the Rabbit Hole", "start_date": "2013-06-17 19:00:00", "status": "Completed",
        "description": "<P>This is the description.</P>", "end_date": "2013-06-17
        22:00:00", "tags": "", "timezone_offset": "GMT+0100", "text_color": "005580",
        "title_text_color": "", "password": "", "tickets": [{"ticket": {"description":
        "", "end_date": "2013-06-17 18:00:00", "min": 1, "max": null, "price": "0.00",
        "quantity_sold": 1, "visible": "true", "start_date": "2013-02-11 09:00:00",
        "currency": "GBP", "quantity_available": 100, "display_price": "0.00", "type":
        0, "id": 17042304, "include_fee": "true", "name": "Free Ticket"}}, {"ticket":
        {"description": "", "end_date": "2013-06-17 18:00:00", "min": 1, "max": null,
        "price": "1.00", "quantity_sold": 7, "visible": "true", "currency": "GBP",
        "quantity_available": 100, "display_price": "1.00", "type": 0, "id": 17042456,
        "include_fee": "true", "name": "Cheap Ticket"}}], "created": "2013-02-05 09:08:12",
        "url": "https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/test-event-00-drupal-down-the-rabbit-hole-tickets-5441375300?ref=ebapi",
        "box_text_color": "000000", "privacy": "Private", "venue": {"city": "", "name":
        "The office", "country": "", "region": "", "longitude": 0.0, "postal_code":
        "", "address_2": "", "address": "", "latitude": 0.0, "country_code": "", "id":
        2959410, "Lat-Long": "0.0 / 0.0"}, "m<METRICS_API_USERNAME>fied": "2014-05-30
        05:38:28", "repeats": "no"}}'
    http_version: 
  recorded_at: Thu, 07 Aug 2014 15:47:50 GMT
recorded_with: VCR 2.8.0
